Are Many Chance
cha cha cha
ちゃちゃちゃ
amechan nakereba hashirenai
あめちゃんなければ走れない
I can't run without any candy...
amechan aru kara
あめちゃんあるから
With a candy
hashireru hashireru
走れる走れる
I can run, I can run
amechan toketara hashirenai
あめちゃんとけたら走れない
If the candy melts then I can't run
amechan sagashi ni
あめちゃん探しに
To find more Candy
hashirou hashirou
走ろう走ろう
Let's run and run
touzai nanboku shunka shuutou
東西南北春夏秋冬祝祭休日返上で
In North-South-East-West, In Spring-Summer-Autumn-Winter
shukusai kyuujitsu henjou de
Giving up all the holidays and festivals
amechan tazunete sanzenri
あめちゃんたずねて三千里
To search for candies across 3000 leagues
shokugo ni dessert ohitotsu
食後にデザートおひとつ
After a meal, my dessert will be a
amechan
あめちゃん
Candy
amechan tabetara mo hitotsu
あめちゃん食べたらもひとつ
After eating a candy, I'll have one more
amechan
あめちゃん
Candy
amazing chance
アメイジングチャンス
Amazing chance
!!!!!! ★ ♪ ◎ × ▲ ☆ !!!!!!
sakebe!!! amechan GET!!! Are Many Chance
さけべ!!! あめちゃん GET!!! Are Many Chance
Shout it out!!! Candy GET!!! Are Many Chance
ubaiai mode
奪い合いモード
Scrambling mode
honki shoubu
本気勝負
The true showdown
mecha mecha kyuuto na
めちゃめちゃキュートな
A super duper cute
oaji no
お味の
Flavoured candy
amechan
あめちゃん
Candy
mezase!!! amechan GET!!! Are Many Chance
目指指!!! あめちゃん GET!!! Are Many Chance
Aim for it!!! Candy GET!!! Are Many Chance
te ni shita shunkan bakuhatsu
手にした瞬間爆発
The moment it's picked up, it explodes
sekaijuu de ichiban☆
世界中で一番☆
The best in the world
a~mecha DREAMIN' TIME
あ〜めちゃ DREAMIN' TIME
Ah, candy dreamin' time
hyaku percent amechan
百パーセントあめちゃん
100% Candy
a~mecha mecha mecha
あ〜めちゃめちゃめちゃ
Ah candy, candy
Are Many Chance!!! Ah mecha amechan
Are Many Chance!!! Ah めちゃあめちゃん
Are Many Chance!!! Ah Candy, Candy